Finding Aid for the Kelly Miller Smith Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- WRITINGS
  - January 28, 1968 - February 4, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - March; September 21; October 26, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - November - December, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - March 15-29, 1970; July 12, 1970; December 6, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - March - April, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - October - December, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - February - March, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - April - May, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - June - July, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - August - October, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - November - December, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - January - February, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - First Baptist Church, The Torch, 1973 - 1975
  - March - May, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - June - July, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - August - September, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - October - December, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - January - February, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - March - April, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - May - June, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - July - August, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - September - October, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - November - December, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - January - February, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - March - April, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - May - June, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - July - August, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - September - October, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - November - December, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - First Baptist Church, The Torch, 1976 - 1978
  - January - February, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - March - April, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - May - June, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - July - August, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - September - October, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - November - December, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - January - February, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - March - April, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - May - June, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - July - August, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - September - October, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - November - December, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - January - February, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - March - April, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - First Baptist Church, The Torch, 1978 - 1980
  - May - June, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - July - August, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - September - October, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - November - December, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - January - February, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - March - April, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - May - June, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - July - August, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - September - October, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - November - December, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - January - February, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - March - April, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - May - June, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - July 27 - September, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - First Baptist Church, The Torch, 1980 - 1983
  - October - December, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - January - February, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - March - April, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - May - June, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - July - August, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - September - October, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - November - December, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - January - February, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - March - April, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - May - June, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - July - August, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - September - October, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - November - December, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - January - February, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - March - April, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - May - June, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - The Torch, 1983 - 1985
  - July - August, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - September - October, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - November - December, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - January - February, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - March - April, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - May - June, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - July - August, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - September, October, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - November, December, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - January, May, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - The Beacon, 1979 - 1982 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - The Messenger, 1954 - 1955, Family Firesides (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Calendars, 1959 - 1966 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Calendars, 1967 - 1969 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - First Baptist Church
  - Calendars, 1970 - 1974 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Calendars, 1975 - 1978 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Calendars, 1979 - 1983 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Church Directories, 1923 - 1972 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Church Directories, 1973 - 1975, undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Membership Handbooks, 1960 - 1961 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Membership Handbooks, 1962 - 1964 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - First Baptist Church
  - Membership Handbook, 1964 - 1967 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Membership Handbook, 1967 - 1973 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Membership Handbook, 1973 - 1975 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Membership Handbook, 1976 - 1977 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Membership Handbook, 1979 - 1980 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Church Program, 1953 - 1955, undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Church Program, 1955 - 1957 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - First Baptist Church
  - Church Program, 1963-1974, undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Church Program, undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Committees on Furnishings, Dedication Committee (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Deacons (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Evangelism (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Financial Planning Committee (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Financial Reports, Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Financial Reports, 1974, Proposed Budget, 1974 - 1975 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Financial Reports, 1975, Proposed Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Financial Reports, 1976 - 1982 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Floor Plans, Eighth Ave. North and James Robertson Parkway (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Glimpses into the Past (First Baptist Church, 1844-1959: A Historical Dramatization) (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Kelly Miller Smith Towers (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Kennedy Concert (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Matrons, 1978 - 1980 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Ministers (Reflections of the First Baptist Church Ministers) (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Ministry of Communications, Public Relations Committee (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Minutes, Mortgage Burning Committee (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Notes/Items (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Petty Cash Receipts (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Procedures for the Operations of Auxiliaries and Organizations (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Receipts (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Regulations for Use of Church Building (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Rules and Regulations - - Outside Use of First Baptist Church, Capitol Hill (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Transmittal Slips, 1966 - 1977 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Virgil Hensley, Inc. - Church, Financial (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - First Baptist Church
  - Annual Financial Report, 1960 - 1961 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Church Meetings (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Church Membership Class (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1964 - 1980, undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Custodial Work Sheet, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Finances; Finance Committee (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Flowers (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Historical Information (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Ministry of Education (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, Executive Board of the Building Committee (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous (Flyers, Brochures, etc.) (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - - 14 Miscellaneous Notes and Minutes (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Physical Facilities (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Social Action Committee (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Social Action Committee (Book Reading) (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Spring Lecture Series, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Spring Lecture Series, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Strike Anywhere Squad (Box 47, Folder 20)
- SUBJECT FILES
  - A. Philip Randolph Institute Academy of Parish Clergy, Inc., 1974-1980 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Academy of Parish Clergy, Inc. (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Academy of Parish Clergy, Inc., 1974 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Academy of Parish Clergy, Inc., 1975 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Academy of Parish Clergy, Inc., 1976 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Academy of Parish Clergy, Inc., 1977 (Box 48, Folder 5 - 6)
  - Academy of Parish Clergy, Inc., 1978 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Academy of Parish Clergy, Inc., "Sharing the Practice," 1979-1980 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Admirals Club (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Advisory Board for Theological Studies, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Advisory Committee - Metropolitan Welfare Commission (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Advisory Committee - State Board of Regents (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - African Consultation and Black American Baptist Churchmen (BABC) Committee Meeting, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - African Liberation Committee (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - African Studies (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Africare (Box 48, Folder 16 - 19)
  - Alliance for Black Social Welfare (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Alternatives for Jailed Children (Box 49, Folder 1 - 2)
  - "America's Great Hour" (sermon by Dr. Mordecai W. Johnson) (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - American Academy of Political and Social Sciences (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - American Association of Retired Persons (AARP) (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - American Association of Retired Persons (AARP) - - Publications (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - American Association of Theological Schools — Task Force #7 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - American Association of University Professors - - Executive Committee (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - American Baptist Assembly (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - American Baptist Churches of the South (ABCOTS), 1970 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - American Baptist Churches of the South (ABCOTS), 1973 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - American Baptist Churches of the South (ABCOTS), 1974 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - American Baptist Churches of the South (ABCOTS), 1975 - 1982 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - - 15 American Baptist Churches of the South (ABCOTS), 1984 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - American Baptist Churches, USA, 1970-1981 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - American Baptist Churches, USA (Biennial Meeting), 1977 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - American Baptist Churches, USA (Foreign Mission Society) (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - American Baptist Churches, USA (Ministers and Missionaries Baptist Board (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - American Baptist Churches, USA - - Clippings (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - - 22 American Baptist Churches, USA - - Publications (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - American Baptist Churches, USA - - Publications (Box 50, Folder 1 - 2)
  - American Baptist Convention, USA (General Information) (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - American Baptist Convention, USA, 1964 - 1966 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - American Baptist Convention, USA, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - American Baptist Convention, USA, 1970 - 1971 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - American Baptist Convention, USA, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - American Baptist Convention, USA, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - American Baptist Convention, USA, undated (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - American Baptist Convention, USA, Clippings (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - American Baptist Convention, USA, Publications (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - American Baptist Convention, USA, Publications (The American Baptist) (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - American Baptist Convention, USA, Publications (The Crusader, 1963 - 1966) (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - - 15 American Baptist Convention, USA, Publications (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - American Baptist Directory of Theological Seminaries and Schools (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - American Baptist Foreign Mission Society (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - American Baptist Literature (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - American Baptist Mission Society (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - American Baptist News Service, (Press Releases, 1972 - 1980) (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - American Baptist Theological Seminary; American Baptist College (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - American Bible Society (Scriptures - - Visual Aids - - Literature Information) (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - - 9 American Bible Study (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - American Biographical Institute (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - American Cancer Society, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - American Cancer Society, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - American Cancer Society, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - American Cancer Society, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - American Cancer Society (Public Education Committee), 1983 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - American Cancer Society, Cancer News, 1982 - 1984 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), 1972 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), 1975 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), 1976 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) - - Publications (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - American Immigration and Citizenship Committee (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - American Laboratory Institute Students (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - American National Red Cross (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - American Negro Leadership Conference on Africa (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - American Red Cross - - Nashville - Davidson County Chapter, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - American Red Cross - - Nashville - Davidson County Chapter, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 6 - 7)
  - American Red Cross - - Nashville - Davidson County Chapter, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - American Red Cross - - Nashville - Davidson County Chapter, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 9 - 10)
  - American Red Cross - - Nashville - Davidson County Chapter, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 11 - 12)
  - American Red Cross - - Nashville - Davidson County Chapter, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 13 - 14)
  - American Red Cross - - Nashville - Davidson County Chapter, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - American Red Cross -- Nashville - Davidson County Chapter, Miscellaneous Pamphlets (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - American Red Cross -- Nominating Committee, 1976 - 1977 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - American Red Cross -- Personnel Committee (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Anti-Apartheid (Box 53, Folder 1 - 3)
  - Anti-Klan Information Packet (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Article on the Responsibilities of Business -- Comments by KMS (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Association of American Universities (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Atlanta American (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Atlanta's Black Society — Clippings (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Bass - Jones Concert (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Beck Cultural Exchange Center, Inc. (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Behavioral Science Bonus Certificates (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Berea College (Box 53, Folder 12 - 13)
  - Bethlehem Center (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Bibliographies (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Birthrite (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Black American Baptist Caucus Executive Committee (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Black American Baptist Churchmen, 1969 - 1971 (Box 53, Folder 18 - 20)
  - Black Church Studies Committee Conference (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Black Church — Clippings (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Black Churches/Colleges/Universities — June 30 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Black Churches and Black Colleges/Universities Network (National Black Pastors' Conference (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Black Churchmen for Economic Development (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Black Community Conference (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Black Community Forum, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Black Community Forum, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Black Community Forum, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Black Community Forum, News Releases (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Black Community Strategy (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Black Ecumenical Commission (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Black Education Convention (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Black Expo '74 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Black Expo '75 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Black Expo '76 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Black Expo '77 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Black Expo '77 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Black Expo '78 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Black Expo '79 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Black Expo '80 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Black Expo — Clippings (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Black Leadership Forum (Carole Hoover) (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Black Leadership Forum (Carole Hoover) (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Black Madonna (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Black Publications (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Black Publications (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Black Renaissance of the 1920s (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Black Studies (Various) (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Black Studies and Related Disciplines (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Black Women — Clippings (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Brookmeade Newsletter (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Bunch Cadillac, Inc. (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Cameron - Stratford Affair (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Capital Punishment (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Carte Blanche (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Center for Parish Development (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Center for Parish Development (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors (CCCO) (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Chautauga Mission Conference (August 20 - 25, 1972) (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Chicago Baptist Institute (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Chicago Sunday Evening Club, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Chicago Sunday Evening Club, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Chicago Sunday Evening Club, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Child Development from a Black Perspective — Conference Sponsored by Black Child Development Education Center — D.C. (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Children's Defense Fund (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Children's Defense Fund (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Christian Education Fellowship (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Christian Education Support Group (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Christian Stewardship Development (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Christian Center for United Nations (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Churches with Vacant Pulpits (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Citizens Committee (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Citizens Energy Meetings (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Citizens in Crisis (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Citizens Savings Bank and Trust Co. (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - City-Wide Evangelistic Revival (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Civil Disobedience Study (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Civil Rights (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Civil Rights (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Civil Rights (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Civil Rights, Clippings, 1957 - 1960 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Civil Rights, 1961 - 1962 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Civil Rights, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Civil Rights, 1964 - 1967 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Civil Rights, 1968 - 1969 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Civil Rights, 1970 - 1975 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Civil Rights, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Civil Rights, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Civil Rights, 1981 - 1982 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Civil Rights, undated (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Clergy and Laity Concerned (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Clergy Group (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Clippings (Miscellaneous), 1961 - 1969 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Clippings (Miscellaneous), 1970 - 1979 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Clippings (Miscellaneous), 1980 - 1982 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Clippings (Miscellaneous), undated (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Commission for Racial Justice (UCC), 1975 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Commission for Racial Justice, 1976 - 1978 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Commission on Faith and Order (World Council of Churches - WCC) (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Commission on Faith and Order (World Council of Churches - WCC) (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Commission on Faith and Order (World Council of Churches - WCC) — Ghana (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Commission on the Ministry (American Baptist Convention) (Box 57, Folder 1 - 3)
  - Committee on African Liberation (COAL) (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Committee on African Liberation (COAL) — Clippings (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Committee to Investigate Conditions at Central State Hospital (Box 57, Folder 6 - 9)
  - Committee to Study Metro Jail (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Common Cause, 1972 - 1977 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Common Cause, undated (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Common Cause, undated (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Common Cause - - Publications (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Communique (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Community Relations Committee Meeting and Metropolitan Action Commission (MAC) (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - CONCERN (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Conference Planning Committee - - Black Community Conference (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Congo Health Committee (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Congo Trip (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Congress of National Black Churches (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Congress of Racial Equality (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Congressional Black Caucus (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Constitutional Convention Letters (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Consumer Outreach Planning Committee (National Medical Association, Inc. (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Context (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Council for Church and Ministry (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Council of Community Services, 1966 - 1975 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Council of Community Services, 1976 - 1984 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Council of Community Services (Ad Hoc Committer) (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Council on Religion and International Affairs (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Cumberland Museum (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Cumberland Museum (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - D. Parke Gibson Associates, Inc. (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Data Black (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - David B. Todd Foundation (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Davidson County Legislative Delegation (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Decision '74 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Delta Ministry (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Democratic National Committee (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Dimensions of International Affairs Education (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Diners Club (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Divorce (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - East End Baptist Tabernacle, Bridgeport, Connecticut (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Ebony Gazette (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Economic Development Conference and the Black Manifesto (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Editorial Projects for Education (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Emotionally Disturbed Children (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Employment Aid (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Evolution in Ebony (Television Documentary) (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee, Advisory Board for Theological Studies, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Executive Tax Report (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Fact Sheet 109 — Louis Martin (Special Assistant to the President) (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Forum (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Family and Children's Service, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Family and Children's Service, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Family and Children's Service, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Family and Children's Service, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Family and Children's Service, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Family and Children's Service, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Family and Children's Service, Board of Directors (January 1972 - May 1972) (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Family and Children's Service, Board of Directors (June 1972 - July 1972) (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Family and Children's Service, Board of Directors (August 1972 - November 1972) (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Family and Children's Service, Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Family and Children's Service, Board of Directors (February 1973 - September 1977) (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Family and Children's Service, Public Issues Committee, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Family and Children's Service, Public Issues Committee, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Family and Children's Service, Public Issues Committee, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Family and Children's Service, Public Issues Committee, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Fayette County, Haywood County, Tennessee (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Federated and Non-Federated Club Women of Nashville (Roster of Club Presidents), 1961 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Fellowships and Grants (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Fireside Bible Publishers (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Fisk Review Committee on External Relations (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Fisk Strikers (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Fisk University (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Florence Crittenton Home (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Foster Grandparent Project (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Foundations and Grants (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Full Employment Action Council (Box 60, Folder 11 - 13)
  - Fund for Theological Education, Inc. (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Fund of Renewal, 1972 - 1973 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Fund of Renewal, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 16 - 18)